<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RBX Counter - Get Rbux Calc</string>
    <string name="strRBXHint">Enter RBX Amount...</string>
    <string name="count_now">Count Now</string>
    <string name="strDollarHint">Enter Dollar Amount...</string>
    <string name="dollar_to_rbx_conversion">Dollar to RBX Conversion</string>
    <string name="dollars">Dollars</string>
    <string name="this_amount_of_dollars_will_convert_to">This amount of dollars will convert to</string>
    <string name="rbx">RBX</string>
    <string name="rbx_to_dollar_cost">RBX to Dollar Cost</string>
    <string name="buying_this_much_rbx_will_cost">Buying this much RBX will cost</string>

    <string name="title_rbxtodoller">RBX TO Dollar Calculator</string>
    <string name="title_dollertorbx">Dollar TO RBX Calculator</string>


    <string name="BCDailyRBXCounter">BC RBX Counter</string>
    <string name="OBCDailyRBXCounter">OBC RBX Counter</string>
    <string name="TBCDailyRBXCounter">TBC RBX Counter</string>
    <string name="bc_to_rbx_cost">BC to RBX Cost</string>
    <string name="tbc_to_rbx_cost">TBC to RBX Cost</string>
    <string name="obc_to_rbx_cost">OBC to RBX Cost</string>

    <string name="ch_addison">Addison is a stylish and trendy character known for her vibrant and confident personality.\nHer design features fashionable clothing and a cheerful expression, making her perfect for social settings.\nGreat for casual and trendy looks, fitting well in modern city adventures.\nPairs well with stylish accessories, sunglasses, and sneakers.\n\nOften seen in roleplaying games and hangout experiences.\nBest suited for users who love an upbeat and fashionable aesthetic.\nHer versatile appearance makes her a popular choice among players.\nEasy to mix and match with different outfits and emotes.\nAddison’s energetic vibe adds personality to any gameplay experience.</string>

    <string name="ch_blazerburner">Blazer Burner is a fiery character with a bold and energetic look, perfect for those who love intense action.\nDesigned for speed and agility, making him ideal for competitive and racing games.\nFeatures a sporty and futuristic outfit with sleek details.\nPopular in high-speed challenges and battle-style adventures.\n\nMatches well with flame-themed accessories and fast-paced animations.\nGives off a confident and fearless vibe, making him a standout choice.\nHis design represents power, speed, and determination.\nPerfect for users who enjoy action-packed and high-energy gameplay.\nOften used in games focused on speed, fire, and competition.</string>

    <string name="ch_calico">Calico is a fun and adorable feline-inspired character, perfect for cat lovers.\nFeatures soft pastel colors and a playful expression.\nGreat for cozy and casual-themed experiences.\nWorks well with cute outfits, bows, and pet accessories.\n\nIdeal for users who enjoy kawaii and animal-inspired avatars.\nPerfect for roleplaying as a pet-loving or whimsical character.\nOften seen in social games and cute-themed worlds.\nBrings a soft and lovable presence to any game.\nA great choice for those who want a charming and friendly look.</string>

    <string name="ch_capybara">Capybara is a fun, animal-inspired character that brings a relaxed and chill vibe to any game.\nIts simple yet adorable design makes it a favorite among animal lovers.\nPerfect for casual, fun, and meme-themed experiences.\nOften used in roleplaying games where players take on the role of cute animals.\n\nGoes well with nature-themed accessories and playful animations.\nIts laid-back expression makes it perfect for relaxed gameplay.\nFrequently seen in social hangouts and comedic settings.\nPairs well with fun emotes like dances and funny poses.\nA great choice for players who enjoy a lighthearted and carefree experience.</string>

    <string name="ch_cindy">Cindy is a stylish and friendly character designed for players who love modern fashion.\nHer outfit is casual yet trendy, making her a versatile choice for any setting.\nPopular in roleplaying games where players create social or school-based characters.\nGreat for users who want a friendly and approachable appearance.\n\nWorks well with modern accessories like handbags, sneakers, and sunglasses.\nCommonly seen in city life, school, and fashion-themed games.\nHer cheerful and upbeat design makes her a fun choice.\nEasy to customize with different hairstyles and outfits.\nA great fit for players who enjoy social interactions and stylish avatars.</string>

    <string name="ch_city_life_woman">City Life Woman is a stylish and modern character designed for urban-themed experiences.\nHer fashionable outfit makes her perfect for city-based roleplaying games.\nOften used in social and simulation games set in bustling city environments.\nWorks well with trendy accessories like handbags, sunglasses, and high heels.\n\nIdeal for players who want an elegant yet casual avatar.\nPopular in games where players interact in virtual communities and build friendships.\nPairs well with business attire or casual chic styles for a sophisticated look.\nHer confident and friendly appearance makes her great for storytelling and roleplay.\nPerfect for players who enjoy modern fashion and city-inspired adventures.</string>

    <string name="ch_claire">Claire is an elegant and classy character, perfect for players who enjoy sophisticated looks.\nHer refined outfit makes her stand out in formal and stylish settings.\nGreat for roleplaying as a high-class, fashionable character.\nPairs well with fancy accessories like pearl necklaces and high heels.\n\nOften seen in fashion, business, and upper-class roleplay games.\nPerfect for those who want a polished and confident appearance.\nCan be customized with elegant hairstyles and evening wear.\nPopular among players who enjoy luxury and socialite themes.\nA great character for expressing sophistication and style.</string>

    <string name="ch_dennis">Dennis is a classic Roblox character with a friendly and approachable design.\nOften seen in casual and adventure-themed games, making him a versatile choice.\nHis simple yet stylish outfit works well in a variety of game settings.\nGreat for beginners who want a recognizable and easy-to-use avatar.\n\nPopular in role-playing and social hangout games where players interact.\nPairs well with casual accessories like backpacks, sneakers, and hats.\nPerfect for players who enjoy a laid-back and fun aesthetic.\nOften chosen for games with open-world exploration and interactive experiences.\nHis friendly expression and neutral style make him a go-to character for many.</string>

    <string name="ch_denny">Denny is a cool and sporty character with a laid-back but confident attitude.\nHis casual look makes him a perfect choice for everyday roleplays.\nPopular in school, sports, and social games.\nLooks great with athletic accessories like sneakers and backpacks.\n\nHis design is simple but versatile, making him easy to customize.\nOften seen in games where players create school or teen characters.\nPairs well with skateboards, headphones, and street-style outfits.\nPerfect for those who like a relaxed yet stylish avatar.\nA fun and relatable character for many different game settings.</string>

    <string name="ch_john">John is a classic Roblox character known for his simple yet recognizable appearance.\nGreat for players who prefer a traditional and nostalgic Roblox look.\nOften used in beginner-friendly and classic games.\nHis design makes him easy to customize with different outfits and accessories.\n\nPopular in both old-school and modern roleplaying experiences.\nLooks great in casual wear, sports outfits, and adventure gear.\nPerfect for users who want a default but stylish character.\nOften used in social and action-packed games.\nA timeless choice for both new and experienced players.</string>

    <string name="ch_junkbot">Junkbot is a fun and quirky robot character made from recycled parts.\nPerfect for sci-fi and dystopian-themed games.\nGives off a rugged and industrial look.\nPopular in futuristic and adventure-based roleplays.\n\nLooks great with robotic accessories and metal-themed outfits.\nA favorite among players who enjoy unique and creative designs.\nPairs well with mechanical emotes and animations.\nOften used in tech-based or experimental roleplaying games.\nA fun and inventive choice for players who want something different.</string>

    <string name="ch_knights_of_redcliff">The Knights of Redcliff are heroic warriors known for their bravery and strength.\nPerfect for medieval, fantasy, and battle-themed games.\nWears shining armor with a noble and regal presence.\nCommonly seen in castle sieges and adventure roleplays.\n\nPairs well with swords, shields, and capes.\nA great character for those who love epic quests and battles.\nPopular in roleplaying games where players take on the role of knights.\nGives a classic and powerful warrior look.\nPerfect for players who enjoy medieval legends and fantasy adventures.</string>

    <string name="ch_lindsey">Lindsey is a cheerful and friendly character with a fun, casual style.\nGreat for modern, social, and roleplaying experiences.\nHer versatile look fits into a variety of games and settings.\nPairs well with casual accessories like sunglasses and trendy outfits.\n\nPerfect for those who want a bright and welcoming avatar.\nOften used in games where players create everyday scenarios.\nPopular among users who like a cute and stylish look.\nWorks well in school, city life, and adventure-based games.\nA great choice for players who enjoy fashionable and friendly avatars.</string>

    <string name="ch_linlin">Linlin is a stylish and energetic character, perfect for players who love a trendy look.\nHer vibrant outfit and dynamic design make her stand out in social and fashion games.\nA great choice for players who enjoy customization and experimenting with new styles.\nOften used in role-playing games, dance games, and virtual fashion showcases.\n\nHer expressive appearance adds personality to any game environment.\nPairs well with colorful accessories, trendy hairstyles, and modern outfits.\nPopular among players who like to express themselves through their avatars.\nGreat for games where creativity and self-expression are key elements.\nHer fashionable look makes her a favorite for players who enjoy a stylish aesthetic.</string>

    <string name="ch_monster_hugs">Monster Hugs is a playful and quirky character, perfect for those who love a fun twist.\nDesigned with a cute yet monstrous look, making it stand out in any game.\nIdeal for players who enjoy humor and lighthearted interactions.\nOften used in adventure, role-playing, and themed event games.\n\nIts unique appearance adds a fun and imaginative touch to gameplay.\nPairs well with playful accessories, colorful effects, and themed outfits.\nGreat for players who want a mix of spooky and adorable in their avatar.\nPerfect for Halloween events, monster-themed games, or comedic roleplays.\nIts oversized features and friendly monster vibe make it a standout choice.</string>

    <string name="ch_oliver">Oliver is a charming and laid-back character, perfect for casual and friendly gameplay.\nHis relaxed style makes him a great choice for social games and open-world adventures.\nA popular pick for role-playing as a student, a traveler, or a city dweller.\nHis outfit and hairstyle give him a modern and approachable look.\n\nPairs well with casual accessories like backpacks, hoodies, and sneakers.\nGreat for players who enjoy a simple yet stylish avatar design.\nOften used in school, town, and lifestyle simulation games.\nPerfect for those who prefer a friendly and easygoing character.\nA solid choice for any player looking for a well-balanced avatar.</string>

    <string name="ch_peyton">Peyton is a fashionable and confident character, ideal for those who love a trendy look.\nHer stylish design makes her stand out in fashion-based and social games.\nOften used in role-playing as a popular student, influencer, or fashionista.\nHer outfit reflects a modern and upbeat personality.\n\nPairs well with chic accessories, high heels, and stylish sunglasses.\nGreat for players who enjoy expressing themselves through their avatar.\nA favorite for virtual meet-ups, social hangouts, and fashion challenges.\nPerfect for those who want a bold and stylish presence in any game.\nHer confident stance and trendy style make her a standout choice.</string>

    <string name="ch_roblox_boy">Roblox Boy is a classic character, making him a great choice for any player.\nHis simple and iconic look makes him easily recognizable in any game.\nOften used as a default character, but still a solid choice for customization.\nWorks well in all types of gameplay, from adventure to social hangouts.\n\nPairs well with any outfit, making it easy to personalize.\nGreat for players who want a familiar and straightforward avatar.\nPopular among newcomers and those who prefer a minimalist design.\nPerfect for experiencing the core Roblox gameplay in a classic style.\nA versatile character that fits into any game mode or setting.</string>

    <string name="ch_squad_ghouls">Squad Ghouls is a spooky and stylish character, perfect for fans of the supernatural.\nDesigned with a ghostly and edgy look, making them great for Halloween themes.\nOften used in horror, mystery, and fantasy-themed games.\nA great pick for role-playing as a haunted figure or eerie spirit.\n\nPairs well with dark-themed outfits, glowing effects, and eerie accessories.\nPopular among players who love gothic, horror, or creepy aesthetics.\nPerfect for haunted house games, paranormal roleplays, and ghostly adventures.\nTheir unique design makes them stand out in any eerie or supernatural setting.\nGreat for adding a touch of mystery and spookiness to your avatar collection.</string>

    <string name="ch_summer">Summer is a cheerful and vibrant character, perfect for a bright and energetic look.\nHer beach-inspired design makes her ideal for tropical and vacation-themed games.\nOften used in role-playing as a surfer, traveler, or beachgoer.\nHer outfit reflects a fun and relaxed summer vibe.\n\nPairs well with swimsuits, sunglasses, and sun hats for a perfect beach look.\nGreat for players who enjoy sunny and positive aesthetics.\nPerfect for tropical islands, beach parties, and summer festivals.\nHer carefree and adventurous style makes her a fun addition to any game.\nA favorite among players who love bright and cheerful character designs.</string>
    <string name="emote_ala_yoga_pose">This emote showcases a balanced and meditative yoga pose, perfect for relaxation and mindfulness.\nThe animation smoothly transitions into a stable position, maintaining perfect posture.\nIdeal for avatars who want to display calmness, self-control, or spiritual energy.\nGreat for yoga-inspired roleplays, peaceful moments, or wellness-themed environments.\n\nPerfect for expressing tranquility and inner peace in social interactions.\nWorks well with serene landscapes or meditation-themed outfits.\nGives a slow and graceful movement that exudes harmony and balance.\nIdeal for group meditations, dance performances, or fitness challenges.\nComplements avatars who embrace a relaxed and mindful lifestyle.</string>

    <string name="emote_baby_queen">This emote delivers a confident, playful, and royal expression, fit for a true queen.\nThe animation features a stylish pose with a touch of sass and grace.\nPerfect for fashion-forward avatars who want to show off their diva energy.\nGreat for roleplaying as a pop star, royalty, or a confident personality.\n\nWorks well in fashion shows, parties, or dance battles.\nThe movements feel bold and empowered, making any avatar stand out.\nGoes well with tiaras, elegant dresses, and stylish accessories.\nIdeal for players who want to radiate confidence and star power.\nComplements any fashionable, high-energy, or stage-ready outfit.</string>

    <string name="emote_bodybuilder">This emote showcases a strong and muscular flexing pose, perfect for showing off strength.\nThe animation highlights biceps and chest with exaggerated flexing motions.\nIdeal for avatars who want to appear powerful, athletic, or competitive.\nGreat for fitness lovers, gym roleplays, or strength-based challenges.\n\nWorks well in sports arenas, bodybuilding contests, or wrestling matches.\nComplements muscular avatars, gym outfits, or superhero-themed characters.\nExpresses confidence, energy, and physical dominance in any setting.\nPerfect for celebrating victories or taunting opponents in competitions.\nGives a dynamic and strong visual impression, making avatars stand out.</string>

    <string name="emote_cartwheel">This emote features an acrobatic cartwheel, showcasing agility and balance.\nThe movement is smooth, energetic, and adds a playful touch to any avatar.\nIdeal for gymnasts, dancers, and sporty characters who love movement.\nGreat for showcasing athleticism, excitement, or joy in any scenario.\n\nWorks well in gymnastics routines, dance-offs, or parkour challenges.\nComplements avatars with active, flexible, or sporty aesthetics.\nBrings a dynamic, fluid motion that looks both fun and impressive.\nPerfect for showing enthusiasm, excitement, or performing tricks.\nGoes well with energetic and adventurous personality types.</string>

    <string name="emote_flex_walk">This emote features a stylish and confident strut, perfect for showing off attitude.\nThe walking motion includes smooth, exaggerated steps with a cool rhythm.\nIdeal for avatars who want to look trendy, fashionable, and charismatic.\nGreat for making a statement in social settings, fashion shows, or game lobbies.\n\nWorks well with streetwear, high-fashion outfits, or celebrity-inspired styles.\nExpresses a strong sense of self-confidence and swagger.\nBrings a unique and stylish movement to any avatar’s repertoire.\nPerfect for avatars that embrace modern trends and aesthetics.\nComplements any personality that enjoys being the center of attention.</string>

    <string name="emote_floor_rock_freeze">This emote showcases an impressive breakdancing pose, freezing in a dynamic position.\nThe animation highlights balance, core strength, and control.\nIdeal for avatars who love dance battles, hip-hop culture, and freestyle movement.\nGreat for showcasing skill in urban dance environments and competitions.\n\nWorks well with streetwear, sneakers, and urban-inspired fashion.\nExpresses creativity and self-expression in a bold and energetic way.\nBrings a professional and stylish touch to any dance routine.\nPerfect for avatars that want to impress with unique, acrobatic moves.\nComplements a street-savvy, rebellious, or expressive character style.</string>

    <string name="emote_flowinh_breeze">This emote features a graceful and fluid movement, as if the avatar is moving with the wind.\nThe animation flows naturally, making it perfect for elegant characters.\nIdeal for roleplays involving fantasy, dance, or mystical themes.\nGreat for artistic expression in scenic or dreamy settings.\n\nWorks well with flowing dresses, ethereal outfits, and light accessories.\nExpresses peace, movement, and elegance in every motion.\nBrings a soft and enchanting aesthetic to the avatar’s actions.\nPerfect for avatars that embody nature, magic, or poetic beauty.\nComplements soft, dreamy, and artistic personality types.</string>

    <string name="emote_salute">This emote features a crisp and respectful salute, perfect for military or formal settings.\nThe movement is sharp, disciplined, and exudes a sense of honor.\nIdeal for avatars roleplaying as soldiers, officers, or disciplined figures.\nGreat for patriotic events, team coordination, or formal presentations.\n\nWorks well with uniforms, suits, and disciplined character aesthetics.\nExpresses respect, acknowledgment, and a sense of duty.\nBrings a structured and serious tone to the avatar’s actions.\nPerfect for military-themed games, formations, and roleplays.\nComplements avatars with a strong, disciplined, or official presence.</string>

    <string name="emote_samba">This emote features lively and rhythmic Samba dance steps, full of energy.\nThe animation showcases fast footwork and expressive hip movements.\nIdeal for party lovers, dancers, and avatars who enjoy celebrating.\nGreat for festivals, dance competitions, or casual fun moments.\n\nWorks well with colorful, festive outfits and carnival-themed accessories.\nExpresses joy, energy, and passion for movement.\nBrings a lively and festive vibe to any gathering.\nPerfect for avatars who want to bring fun and excitement to the scene.\nComplements energetic and social personality types.</string>

    <string name="emote_tilt">This emote features a smooth and stylish head tilt, adding personality to any avatar.\nThe animation is subtle yet expressive, making it perfect for casual and cool interactions.\nIdeal for avatars who want to convey curiosity, confidence, or a laid-back attitude.\nGreat for casual conversations, social gatherings, or reaction moments.\n\nWorks well with fashionable outfits, sunglasses, and relaxed postures.\nExpresses a range of emotions, from playfulness to mild skepticism.\nBrings a natural and effortless vibe to avatar animations.\nPerfect for avatars who want to add personality without being overly dramatic.\nComplements characters with a chill, stylish, or charismatic presence.</string>
    <string name="bundle_cartoony">This animation set exaggerates movements, making your avatar appear bouncy and full of energy.\nThe walk cycle has a playful sway, giving off a cheerful and lighthearted vibe.\nJumping in this bundle feels springy, as if your character is floating momentarily before landing.\nIdle animations include slight, exaggerated movements that keep your avatar looking animated at all times.\n\nWhen running, the arms and legs swing in an over-the-top fashion, making movement look dynamic.\nMany players love this bundle for its fun and comedic appeal in roleplays and social interactions.\nPerfect for avatars with a goofy or vibrant personality who want to stand out in any game.\nThe waving and emote animations add an extra touch of expressiveness, making communication more engaging.\nOverall, this bundle makes your avatar look like a living cartoon character, adding a unique charm to every movement.</string>

    <string name="bundle_catwalk_glam">This animation set gives your avatar a confident and graceful posture, perfect for a runway look.\nThe walking animation is smooth and deliberate, with each step exuding elegance.\nWhen running, the avatar moves with controlled and poised motions, avoiding exaggerated swings.\nIdle animations showcase subtle weight shifts and stylish posing, emphasizing a high-class presence.\n\nJumping feels delicate yet purposeful, as if the avatar is mindful of maintaining elegance even in motion.\nArm and hand gestures are refined, making expressions appear graceful and fluid.\nThe standing stance conveys an air of confidence, as if the avatar is always ready for the spotlight.\nPerfect for fashion shows, social interactions, and high-profile roleplays where style matters.\nThis bundle adds a professional and polished aura to your avatar, making it a favorite among fashion lovers.</string>

    <string name="bundle_elder">This animation set gives your avatar slow and wise movements, portraying an aged character.\nThe walking animation features a slightly hunched posture with measured and deliberate steps.\nRunning appears more like a fast-paced shuffle, emphasizing a sense of experience rather than speed.\nIdle animations include subtle weight shifts, as if your avatar is resting between movements.\n\nJumping is gentle and controlled, avoiding excessive energy or unnecessary motion.\nArm movements are calm and steady, reinforcing the idea of wisdom and patience.\nThis bundle is great for roleplaying as an elder, a wise mage, or a legendary warrior.\nThe emote animations look refined, making gestures appear meaningful rather than exaggerated.\nOverall, this bundle is ideal for avatars with a wise or mystical presence, adding character depth.</string>

    <string name="bundle_mage">This animation set gives your avatar a magical and mystical aura with floating and elegant movements.\nThe walk cycle includes a slight hovering effect, as if your avatar is gliding rather than stepping.\nRunning appears weightless, making it seem like your character is moving with supernatural grace.\nIdle animations feature subtle hand movements, as if preparing a spell or channeling energy.\n\nJumping has a soft, levitating effect, reinforcing the mystical nature of the animation.\nHand gestures feel fluid and precise, enhancing the roleplay experience for magic users.\nThis bundle is perfect for wizards, sorcerers, and fantasy-themed characters.\nStanding posture remains regal and mysterious, making the avatar look powerful at all times.\nOverall, this bundle adds an enchanted and otherworldly feel to your character’s movements.</string>

    <string name="bundle_nfl">This animation set is inspired by professional football players, featuring powerful and athletic movements.\nThe walking animation has a strong and confident stride, resembling a sports star ready for action.\nRunning is fast and energetic, mimicking the sprinting motion of a professional athlete.\nIdle animations include slight shoulder rolls and warm-up movements, reinforcing the sports theme.\n\nJumping is explosive and dynamic, as if the avatar is leaping to catch a football.\nHand gestures are bold and expressive, perfect for team huddles and celebrations.\nThis bundle is ideal for sports lovers and avatars that want a strong, athletic presence.\nEmotes like cheering and victory poses make it great for competitive roleplay and games.\nOverall, this bundle brings a competitive and action-packed energy to any avatar.</string>

    <string name="bundle_rthro">This animation set is designed for Rthro avatars, giving them realistic and fluid human-like movements.\nThe walking animation is natural and balanced, making the avatar move smoothly.\nRunning has a realistic pace, avoiding exaggerated motions seen in other bundles.\nIdle animations feature subtle breathing movements, making the avatar feel more lifelike.\n\nJumping feels natural, with proper weight distribution and soft landings.\nArm and hand movements follow a realistic motion curve, keeping the avatar\'s actions fluid.\nThis bundle is ideal for players who want a more immersive and grounded avatar experience.\nPerfect for modern-themed games where realism is preferred over cartoonish exaggerations.\nOverall, this bundle makes your avatar move with lifelike precision and authenticity.</string>

    <string name="bundle_stylish">This animation set gives your avatar confident and fashionable movements, making every step look intentional.\nThe walking animation is sleek and smooth, as if your avatar is strutting down a runway.\nRunning maintains a sense of grace, ensuring the avatar never looks clumsy.\nIdle animations include subtle posing, making your character look effortlessly stylish.\n\nJumping is controlled and well-balanced, avoiding any awkward or exaggerated landings.\nHand and arm gestures are fluid, giving the impression of a charismatic personality.\nThis bundle is great for avatars that want to exude confidence and charm.\nPerfect for fashion lovers, influencers, and stylish roleplayers in Roblox.\nOverall, this bundle makes your avatar look effortlessly cool in any situation.</string>

    <string name="bundle_superhero">This animation set makes your avatar move like a powerful and heroic figure.\nThe walking animation is strong and assertive, with each step exuding confidence.\nRunning is fast-paced and dynamic, perfect for action-packed games.\nIdle animations feature heroic poses, as if the avatar is ready to defend the city.\n\nJumping feels powerful, with a dramatic liftoff and controlled landing.\nHand gestures are bold and dramatic, enhancing superhero-themed roleplay.\nThis bundle is perfect for comic book fans and action-driven gameplay.\nGreat for characters that want to embody strength, justice, and heroism.\nOverall, this bundle transforms your avatar into a true superhero, ready to save the day.</string>

    <string name="bundle_toy">This animation set gives your avatar a fun, playful, and mechanical toy-like movement style.\nThe walking animation has a bouncy, slightly rigid feel, resembling a wind-up toy.\nRunning is energetic but slightly stiff, enhancing the toy aesthetic.\nIdle animations include slight sways, making the avatar appear lively even when standing still.\n\nJumping feels springy, as if your avatar is made of plastic or rubber.\nHand and arm movements are exaggerated, making interactions feel more animated.\nThis bundle is perfect for whimsical and cartoonish characters.\nGreat for roleplaying as a doll, action figure, or animated toy.\nOverall, this bundle makes your avatar feel fun and lighthearted, like a living toy.</string>

    <string name="bundle_vampire">This animation set gives your avatar a dark and mysterious presence, perfect for gothic roleplays.\nThe walking animation is smooth and deliberate, with an air of supernatural grace.\nRunning has a silent and swift quality, making movement seem effortless.\nIdle animations include subtle head tilts and hand gestures, adding a sinister charm.\n\nJumping feels controlled, as if the avatar is defying gravity with ease.\nHand movements are elegant yet eerie, reinforcing the gothic aesthetic.\nThis bundle is great for vampire, dark mage, or gothic-themed avatars.\nPerfect for roleplaying in haunted castles, underworld realms, or dark fantasy settings.\nOverall, this bundle makes your avatar appear both menacing and mysteriously alluring.</string>

    <string name="accessory_face1">A super cute face with chubby cheeks, perfect for a soft and innocent look.\nThis face gives off a warm, cheerful vibe, making it a great choice for players who want their avatars to look friendly and approachable.\nBest for: Kawaii, baby-themed, or soft-style avatars.\nPopular use: Roleplaying as an adorable or youthful character.\n\nCustomization Tip: Pair it with pastel-colored outfits, oversized sweaters, and cute accessories.\nExtra Styling: This face goes perfectly with bunny ears, fluffy jackets, or heart-shaped glasses for an ultra-kawaii look.\nMany players love using this face in cozy-themed games or when dressing up for virtual hangouts with friends.\nIt also works well for playful and fantasy avatars, making it a great choice for fairy, anime, or magical girl themes.</string>

    <string name="accessory_face10">A stylish face with detailed lower lashes, perfect for an elegant and fashionable avatar.\nThis face gives off a refined and glamorous vibe, making it a great choice for stylish avatars.\nBest for: High-class, beauty guru, or stylish avatars.\nPopular use: Fashion contests, aesthetic roleplays.\n\nCustomization Tip: Pair with long elegant dresses, sparkly accessories, and premium hairstyles.\nExtra Styling: Works well with luxury handbags, gemstone jewelry, and formal event outfits.\nMany players love using this face in runway-themed games or to create influencer-style avatars.\nIt also complements avatars with a modern, celebrity-inspired aesthetic, making it perfect for glam-themed events.</string>

    <string name="accessory_face2">A charming blushing face that adds a touch of shyness and cuteness to your avatar.\nThis expression is perfect for players who want a soft and sweet aesthetic.\nBest for: Shy, romantic, or schoolgirl/boy-themed avatars.\nPopular use: Dating roleplays, anime-inspired characters.\n\nCustomization Tip: Works best with soft hairstyles, school uniforms, and heart-themed accessories.\nExtra Styling: Perfect for recreating anime characters with a timid yet lovable personality.\nPlayers often use this face in romantic roleplays or slice-of-life-themed games.\nIt also pairs well with school outfits, making it a great choice for high school and cafe-inspired avatars.</string>

    <string name="accessory_face3">A stylish and effortless expression that gives your avatar a trendy, cool vibe.\nThis face is ideal for modern, fashion-forward avatars that want to stand out.\nBest for: Fashionable, influencer-style avatars.\nPopular use: Roblox fashion competitions, modeling avatars.\n\nCustomization Tip: Combine with high-fashion clothing, sunglasses, and designer-style handbags.\nExtra Styling: A great choice for players who enjoy aesthetic-based social games.\nMany players love using this face in virtual runway shows and social hangouts.\nIt also works great for influencer-style avatars, pairing well with trendy outfits and stylish accessories.</string>

    <string name="accessory_face4">A simple yet adorable face that fits perfectly with any kawaii or soft-style avatar.\nThis face is designed to be universally cute and goes well with most outfits.\nBest for: Universal cute looks that work with most outfits.\nPopular use: Everyday wear, casual and kawaii styles.\n\nCustomization Tip: Matches well with pastel outfits, bunny ears, and puffy skirts.\nExtra Styling: Looks great with cozy-themed aesthetics and relaxed fashion styles.\nMany players love this face for its versatility, making it a go-to choice for various outfits.\nIt’s also great for avatars that focus on a clean, aesthetic look without being too bold.</string>

    <string name="accessory_face5">A unique cute face featuring deep black eyes for an expressive and mysterious look.\nThe bold black eyes give a strong contrast, making this face stand out.\nBest for: Dark-themed, emo, or gothic avatars.\nPopular use: Mysterious characters, anime and gothic aesthetics.\n\nCustomization Tip: Pair with black outfits, vampire wings, or neon accessories for contrast.\nExtra Styling: Perfect for fantasy and gothic roleplays.\nMany players love using this face in gothic and supernatural roleplaying themes.\nIt also works well for sci-fi and futuristic avatars, making it a great choice for cyberpunk-inspired outfits.</string>

    <string name="accessory_face6">A lovely smiling face with a slight blush, making your avatar look friendly and charming.\nThis face radiates kindness, making it a great choice for social interactions.\nBest for: Cheerful, friendly, and approachable avatars.\nPopular use: Social roleplaying, making friends in-game.\n\nCustomization Tip: Works well with casual wear, bright colors, and animated wings.\nExtra Styling: A great pick for social hangouts and party events.\nMany players love using this face for welcoming and friendly avatars.\nIt’s also a popular choice for avatars in community-based and open-world games.</string>

    <string name="accessory_face7">A cheerful and energetic face that radiates happiness and enthusiasm.\nThis expression brings life and excitement to any avatar.\nBest for: Fun, bubbly, and hyperactive avatars.\nPopular use: Dance battles, party events, and celebration themes.\n\nCustomization Tip: Combine with neon clothing, glowstick accessories, and party hats.\nExtra Styling: Perfect for club and festival-themed avatars.\nMany players love using this face in music-themed and dance games.\nIt also pairs well with bright, colorful outfits for a lively and fun look.</string>

    <string name="accessory_face8">A super kawaii and chibi-style face that enhances your avatars playful and youthful appearance.\nThis expression makes your avatar look extra cute and animated.\nBest for: Cute, childlike, or anime-style avatars.\nPopular use: Anime fan avatars, chibi character designs.\n\nCustomization Tip: Works great with oversized hoodies, mini skirts, and big expressive eyes.\nExtra Styling: Pair with animated emotes to bring out its full effect.\nMany players love using this face for cosplay and anime-themed outfits.\nIt’s also a great choice for creating avatars that resemble popular chibi characters.</string>

    <string name="accessory_face9">A big, joyful laughing face that spreads positive energy to your Roblox world.\nThis expressive face is perfect for players who love to spread happiness and fun.\nBest for: Happy-go-lucky, comedian, or joker-style avatars.\nPopular use: Comedy roleplays, fun interactions with friends.\n\nCustomization Tip: Matches well with clown outfits, fun hats, and bright-colored shoes.\nExtra Styling: Ideal for party themes, carnival characters, and comedic avatars.\nMany players love using this face for prankster and energetic personalities in roleplaying.\nIt also works great in dance-themed games and funny in-game moments, making your avatar stand out in a crowd.</string>

    <string name="accessory_head1">A voluminous pastel pink hairstyle with an adorable bow, giving your avatar a soft, girly touch.\nBest for: Kawaii, princess, or dreamy-themed avatars.\nPopular use: Roleplaying as a cute anime girl, pastel-themed fashion styles.\n\nCustomization Tip: Pair with pink dresses, fluffy skirts, and sparkly accessories for a magical look.\nExtra Styling: Ideal for fairytale and princess-themed outfits, making it great for elegant and sweet aesthetics.\nMany players love using this hairstyle in fantasy settings or magical girl-inspired outfits.\nIt also pairs well with heart-shaped sunglasses, delicate lace gloves, and fairy wings for an enchanting appearance.</string>

    <string name="accessory_head10">A rebellious and edgy punk-style cap that adds attitude and style to your avatar.\nBest for: Punk, rockstar, or skater-style avatars.\nPopular use: Music festivals, skateboarding adventures.\n\nCustomization Tip: Pair with leather jackets, ripped jeans, and studded boots for a complete punk look.\nExtra Styling: Complements grunge and alternative streetwear styles.\nMany players love using this cap for a bold and rebellious fashion statement.\nIt also pairs well with chain necklaces, fingerless gloves, and graffiti-style accessories for a fully punk-inspired vibe.</string>

    <string name="accessory_head2">A dark, stylish captain hat with gothic elements, perfect for adding an edgy vibe to your avatar.\nBest for: Gothic, pirate, or military-style avatars.\nPopular use: Gothic fashionistas, dark aesthetic roleplays.\n\nCustomization Tip: Matches well with black trench coats, combat boots, and chain accessories.\nExtra Styling: Complements vampire and punk outfits, making it great for darker aesthetics.\nMany players love using this hat to create mysterious or powerful characters.\nIt also works well with steampunk or villain-themed outfits, adding a commanding presence.</string>

    <string name="accessory_head3">Adorable fluffy brown dog ears that add a playful and friendly touch to your avatar.\nBest for: Animal lovers, pet roleplays, and cute character designs.\nPopular use: Puppy roleplays, dog-themed avatars.\n\nCustomization Tip: Pairs well with oversized hoodies, paw gloves, and tail accessories.\nExtra Styling: Works great for cozy and playful themes, making your avatar extra cuddly.\nMany players love using these ears for fun pet-themed roleplays or to enhance their cute aesthetic.\nIt also pairs well with fluffy coats and knee-high socks for a full cozy-cute look.</string>

    <string name="accessory_head4">A rugged military-style ushanka with a dark camouflage pattern, giving a tough and tactical look.\nBest for: Military, winter survival, or tactical avatars.\nPopular use: Army roleplays, combat-style outfits.\n\nCustomization Tip: Combine with camouflage jackets, tactical vests, and army boots for an authentic look.\nExtra Styling: Great for survival-themed or snow expedition outfits.\nMany players love using this hat in battle-themed roleplays and cold-weather outfits.\nIt also works well with futuristic soldier themes, adding a rugged but stylish touch.</string>

    <string name="accessory_head5">A classic red hat that adds a stylish and casual element to your avatars outfit.\nBest for: Everyday wear, sporty, or retro-themed avatars.\nPopular use: Casual gaming, vintage-style avatars.\n\nCustomization Tip: Pairs well with denim jackets, sneakers, and sunglasses for a laid-back style.\nExtra Styling: Great for streetwear or 90s-inspired outfits.\nMany players love using this hat to create a cool, relaxed look.\nIt also works great with plaid shirts and skateboards for a skater-inspired style.</string>

    <string name="accessory_head6">A chic pink and brown beret that brings a fashionable and artistic touch to your avatar.\nBest for: French-inspired, stylish, or aesthetic avatars.\nPopular use: Parisian-style outfits, artistic roleplays.\n\nCustomization Tip: Pair with a striped shirt, high-waist pants, and a coffee cup accessory for a trendy look.\nExtra Styling: Complements cozy and bookish aesthetics.\nMany players love using this beret for an intellectual or coffee-shop-inspired look.\nIt also pairs well with turtleneck sweaters and tote bags for a soft and sophisticated style.</string>

    <string name="accessory_head7">A futuristic pink and white bow that gives a high-tech, cyber-inspired feel to your avatar.\nBest for: Sci-fi, cyberpunk, or tech-savvy avatars.\nPopular use: Virtual world explorers, high-tech fashionistas.\n\nCustomization Tip: Matches well with neon outfits, robotic wings, and LED glasses.\nExtra Styling: Perfect for futuristic dance parties or AI-inspired avatars.\nMany players love using this bow in sci-fi and futuristic-themed outfits.\nIt also works well with cybernetic accessories, making your avatar look straight out of a digital world.</string>

    <string name="accessory_head8">A magical unicorn horn that adds a fantasy and mythical touch to your avatar.\nBest for: Fantasy, fairytale, or magical-themed avatars.\nPopular use: Unicorn roleplays, enchanted kingdom themes.\n\nCustomization Tip: Pair with rainbow outfits, fairy wings, and glittery accessories.\nExtra Styling: Ideal for whimsical and enchanted settings.\nMany players love using this horn for magical fantasy characters.\nIt also pairs beautifully with shimmering gowns and celestial effects for an ethereal look.</string>

    <string name="accessory_head9">Sleek and stylish white headphones that give your avatar a modern and music-lover look.\nBest for: Music-themed, DJ, or casual avatars.\nPopular use: Club roleplays, gaming and tech-inspired characters.\n\nCustomization Tip: Goes well with hoodies, ripped jeans, and sunglasses for a cool streetwear vibe.\nExtra Styling: Perfect for EDM and rave-themed avatars.\nMany players love using these headphones for a trendy and relaxed style.\nThey also pair well with LED accessories for a high-energy, concert-ready look.</string>

    <string name="accessory_neck1">A stylish black choker featuring a silver cross pendant, adding a gothic and edgy touch to your avatar.\nBest for: Gothic, punk, or dark aesthetic avatars.\nPopular use: Goth-inspired fashion, vampire roleplays.\n\nCustomization Tip: Pair with dark outfits, combat boots, and silver accessories for a complete gothic look.\nExtra Styling: Looks great with fishnet tops, lace gloves, and dark makeup for an ultimate gothic vibe.\nMany players love using this choker for a mysterious and alternative fashion statement.\nIt also complements Victorian, steampunk, or fantasy-inspired outfits.</string>

    <string name="accessory_neck10">A trendy layered silver necklace that adds a sleek and modern touch to your avatar.\nBest for: Fashion-forward, edgy, or Y2K-inspired avatars.\nPopular use: Streetwear outfits, high-fashion looks.\n\nCustomization Tip: Pair with crop tops, baggy jeans, and statement sunglasses for a bold look.\nExtra Styling: Looks stunning with stacked rings, oversized jackets, and glossy lips for a complete Y2K aesthetic.\nMany players love using this necklace for its ability to elevate even the simplest outfits.\nIt also pairs well with layered streetwear styles and bold accessories.</string>

    <string name="accessory_neck2">Classic black headphones that give your avatar a cool, music-lover aesthetic.\nBest for: Tech-savvy, DJ, or casual street-style avatars.\nPopular use: Gaming setups, music festivals, and futuristic outfits.\n\nCustomization Tip: Goes well with hoodies, joggers, and sunglasses for a modern look.\nExtra Styling: Complements cyberpunk, urban, and e-boy/e-girl aesthetics.\nMany players enjoy using these headphones to add a relaxed, high-tech, or gaming-inspired touch to their avatar.\nThey also work well in virtual concerts and party-themed settings.</string>

    <string name="accessory_neck3">A cute and fluffy Cinnamoroll-themed accessory, perfect for a kawaii and cozy aesthetic.\nBest for: Cute, pastel, and Sanrio-themed avatars.\nPopular use: Roleplaying as a sweet and adorable character.\n\nCustomization Tip: Matches well with pastel dresses, bunny ears, and fluffy accessories.\nExtra Styling: Pairs perfectly with heart-shaped glasses, oversized sweaters, and soft pink tones.\nMany players love using this accessory in wholesome and adorable fashion styles.\nIt also fits perfectly into dreamy and fantasy-inspired outfits.</string>

    <string name="accessory_neck4">A beautiful jade necklace symbolizing peace and good fortune, adding elegance to your avatar.\nBest for: Traditional, elegant, or nature-inspired avatars.\nPopular use: Cultural and mystical themes, elegant fashion styles.\n\nCustomization Tip: Pair with silk robes, floral patterns, and earthy tones for a serene look.\nExtra Styling: Complements eastern-inspired outfits, meditation aesthetics, and fantasy warrior styles.\nMany players love wearing this necklace for its meaningful symbolism and natural beauty.\nIt also enhances outfits with a sophisticated and timeless touch.</string>

    <string name="accessory_neck5">A delicate pearl necklace with a pink ribbon, giving a soft and elegant charm to your avatar.\nBest for: Princess, formal, or royal-themed avatars.\nPopular use: Fancy dress-up, ballroom events, and classy fashion.\n\nCustomization Tip: Goes well with gowns, tiaras, and high heels for a graceful appearance.\nExtra Styling: Looks stunning with lace gloves, pastel-colored dresses, and delicate hairstyles.\nMany players love using this necklace for its refined and luxurious appeal.\nIt also works well for vintage and Victorian-style avatars.</string>

    <string name="accessory_neck6">A stylish striped scarf that adds warmth and fashion to your avatar’s winter outfit.\nBest for: Cozy, winter, or casual avatars.\nPopular use: Snowy adventures, autumn fashion styles.\n\nCustomization Tip: Pair with a wool coat, mittens, and boots for a comfy winter look.\nExtra Styling: Pairs well with beanies, plaid skirts, and thick knitted sweaters.\nMany players love this scarf for its cozy and festive seasonal vibe.\nIt’s also a great choice for warm and nostalgic fashion styles.</string>

    <string name="accessory_neck7">A soft beige scarf that adds a warm and elegant touch to your outfit.\nBest for: Cozy, minimalistic, or aesthetic avatars.\nPopular use: Casual everyday wear, coffee shop vibes.\n\nCustomization Tip: Matches well with trench coats, turtlenecks, and beanies for a fashionable look.\nExtra Styling: Complements soft neutral tones, relaxed styles, and autumn-inspired outfits.\nMany players love using this scarf for a calm and effortlessly chic appearance.\nIt also enhances classic and sophisticated wardrobe choices.</string>

    <string name="accessory_neck8">A rich brown scarf that gives a warm and rustic feel to your avatar’s outfit.\nBest for: Autumn, academia, or vintage-themed avatars.\nPopular use: Cozy fall outfits, intellectual or book-lover styles.\n\nCustomization Tip: Pair with plaid skirts, cardigans, and glasses for a scholarly look.\nExtra Styling: Works great with stacked rings, ripped jeans, and stylish sneakers.\nMany players love using this necklace for its trendy and statement-making appeal.\nIt also complements futuristic and urban aesthetics effortlessly.</string>

    <string name="accessory_neck9">Modern white headphones that bring a stylish and techy vibe to your avatar.\nBest for: Gamers, streamers, and futuristic avatars.\nPopular use: Music lovers, cyber-themed fashion.\n\nCustomization Tip: Matches well with LED outfits, sunglasses, and hoodies for a cool aesthetic.\nExtra Styling: Perfect for creating a sleek, minimalist look when paired with monochrome outfits.\nMany players love using these headphones to enhance digital-inspired and virtual reality-themed styles.\nThey also work well with neon-lit accessories for a cyberpunk aesthetic.</string>

    <string name="ft_adidas_black_flip_flop">Simple yet stylish, these black flip-flops are perfect for a relaxed and casual look.\nIdeal for beach outings, summer adventures, or lounging around in comfort.\nA great footwear choice for avatars who prefer an easygoing and laid-back vibe.</string>

    <string name="ft_adidas_mules_silver">Sleek and modern, these silver mules add a touch of sophistication to any outfit.\nPerfect for streetwear styles, futuristic looks, or high-fashion avatars.\nA great choice for those who want a balance between comfort and elegance.</string>

    <string name="ft_adidas_predator_24_black">Designed for speed and agility, these black cleats are perfect for sporty avatars.\nA great choice for soccer fans and players looking to enhance their athletic aesthetic.\nThe sleek black design makes them a versatile option for casual or competitive looks.</string>

    <string name="ft_adidas_predator_24_greyish">A perfect balance between style and function, these grey cleats offer a sleek look.\nIdeal for sporty avatars who want a more neutral but stylish footwear option.\nWorks well with both casual and athletic outfits for a versatile appearance.</string>

    <string name="ft_adidas_predator_24_yellow_solar">Bold and eye-catching, these yellow cleats are built for those who want to stand out.\nPerfect for avatars who enjoy sports, especially soccer and outdoor adventures.\nThe bright color adds an energetic and dynamic touch to any sporty outfit.</string>

    <string name="ft_adidas_robo">Futuristic and bold, these robotic-style shoes bring a high-tech vibe to your avatar.\nGreat for cyberpunk, sci-fi, or tech-inspired fashion looks.\nThe unique design makes them a standout choice for futuristic or urban styles.</string>

    <string name="ft_canvas_shoes_grey">Classic and versatile, these grey canvas shoes fit seamlessly into any casual outfit.\nPerfect for everyday wear, streetwear styles, and relaxed fashion.\nA great choice for avatars who prefer a subtle and effortless look.</string>

    <string name="ft_canvas_shoes_white">Timeless and fresh, these white canvas shoes are a staple for any wardrobe.\nMatches well with various outfits, from casual streetwear to preppy styles.\nA must-have for avatars who love a clean and stylish aesthetic.</string>

    <string name="ft_charli_xcx_brat_heels">Bold and edgy, these statement heels add a pop of attitude to any outfit.\nPerfect for avatars who love high-fashion, punk, or rebellious aesthetics.\nA great pick for standing out in parties, concerts, or glam-inspired settings.</string>

    <string name="ft_cozy_black_fur_boots">Warm and stylish, these fur-lined boots are great for winter-themed avatars.\nPerfect for cozy outfits, cold-weather adventures, or luxury fashion looks.\nA must-have for anyone looking to stay fashionable in the colder seasons.</string>

    <string name="ft_dress_shoes_brown">Classic and elegant, these brown dress shoes are perfect for formal occasions.\nIdeal for avatars who want to add a sophisticated touch to their outfits.\nA great pick for business attire, fancy events, or polished fashion looks.</string>

    <string name="ft_flats_black">Simple yet stylish, these black flats are a versatile addition to any wardrobe.\nGreat for casual outfits, office wear, or a sleek and effortless look.\nA comfortable and practical choice for everyday wear.</string>

    <string name="ft_flats_blue">Chic and colorful, these blue flats bring a refreshing pop of color.\nIdeal for casual wear, spring outfits, or a playful and feminine look.\nA great way to add a subtle yet stylish element to any wardrobe.</string>

    <string name="ft_flats_zebra">Bold and fashionable, these zebra-patterned flats add a fun twist to any outfit.\nPerfect for avatars who love animal prints and statement fashion.\nA stylish choice that pairs well with edgy, streetwear, or trendy looks.</string>

    <string name="ft_high_tops">Trendy and sporty, these high-top sneakers give off a cool and urban vibe.\nPerfect for streetwear, hip-hop-inspired outfits, or a casual yet stylish look.\nA great choice for avatars who love sneakers and a laid-back aesthetic.</string>

    <string name="ft_huggo_x_ffs">Unique and stylish, these shoes bring a mix of modern and artistic design.\nGreat for fashion-forward avatars who want to stand out with bold footwear.\nA statement piece that complements experimental or futuristic fashion styles.</string>

    <string name="ft_military_boots">Rugged and durable, these boots are perfect for a tough and tactical look.\nIdeal for avatars who enjoy military, survival, or combat-inspired outfits.\nA great addition to any adventurous or action-ready avatar style.</string>

    <string name="ft_ralph_lauren">Elegant and luxurious, these designer shoes add a refined touch to any outfit.\nPerfect for avatars who appreciate high-end fashion and classic styles.\nA premium choice for formal wear, sophisticated events, or stylish ensembles.</string>

    <string name="ft_weyes_blood">Artistic and vintage-inspired, these shoes exude a unique and nostalgic charm.\nPerfect for avatars who love retro, indie, or alternative fashion styles.\nA stylish choice that adds personality to any creative or expressive outfit.</string>

    <string name="ft_work_boots_brown">Sturdy and reliable, these brown work boots offer a rugged and practical look.\nGreat for avatars who prefer tough, outdoorsy, or labor-inspired aesthetics.\nA functional choice that pairs well with utility outfits and casual wear.</string>


    <string name="pant_baggy_jeans">Embrace a relaxed and comfortable style with these baggy jeans, offering a loose fit for everyday wear.\nPerfect for avatars seeking a casual, laid-back look reminiscent of 90s fashion trends.\nPair them with crop tops, chunky sneakers, or vintage shirts to complete the retro ensemble.</string>

    <string name="pant_black_cargo_outfit">Combine functionality and style with this black cargo outfit, featuring multiple pockets and a utilitarian design.\nIdeal for avatars who prefer a practical yet fashionable appearance, suitable for various activities.\nComplements well with casual tops and sturdy footwear for an adventurous look.</string>

    <string name="pant_black_y2k_star_jeans">Channel early 2000s fashion with these black Y2K star jeans, adorned with star patterns for a bold statement.\nGreat for avatars aiming to showcase a trendy and nostalgic style.\nPair with graphic tees or fitted tops to enhance the Y2K aesthetic.</string>

    <string name="pant_blue_alien_sleep_pant">Enjoy comfort and whimsy with these blue sleep pants, featuring playful alien designs.\nPerfect for avatars seeking cozy loungewear with a fun twist.\nIdeal for relaxing in virtual spaces or casual hangouts.</string>

    <string name="pant_blue_butterfly_pants">Add a touch of elegance with these blue butterfly pants, showcasing delicate butterfly motifs.\nSuitable for avatars who appreciate nature-inspired designs and a graceful appearance.\nPairs well with simple tops to let the intricate patterns stand out.</string>

    <string name="pant_blue_denim_cargo_pant">Blend utility and classic style with these denim cargo pants, featuring ample pocket space.\nIdeal for avatars desiring a rugged yet fashionable look.\nComplements casual shirts and boots for a versatile outfit.</string>

    <string name="pant_denim_overall_outfit_pink">Stand out with this pink denim overall outfit, combining playful color with a classic design.\nGreat for avatars looking to express a fun and youthful vibe.\nLayer with t-shirts or sweaters underneath for a complete ensemble.</string>

    <string name="pant_forbidden_full_black_pant">Achieve a sleek and mysterious look with these full black pants, perfect for a monochromatic style.\nIdeal for avatars aiming for a minimalist or edgy appearance.\nPairs effortlessly with various tops and accessories for versatile styling.</string>

    <string name="pant_gangster_jeans">Make a bold statement with these gangster pants, featuring a distinctive design that exudes confidence.\nSuitable for avatars wanting to showcase a rebellious and strong persona.\nBest paired with fitted tops and accessories that match the daring aesthetic.</string>

    <string name="pant_oversized_denim_overall_outfit">Embrace comfort and style with this oversized denim overall, offering a relaxed fit.\nPerfect for avatars seeking a casual and effortlessly cool look.\nLayer with various tops to create diverse and personalized outfits.</string>

    <string name="pant_pajama_pant">Relax in these cozy pajama pants, designed for ultimate comfort during downtime.\nIdeal for avatars who prioritize comfort in their virtual loungewear.\nFeatures soft materials and a relaxed fit for leisurely activities.</string>

    <string name="pant_peach_cargo_pant">Add a pop of color with these peach cargo pants, combining functionality with a vibrant hue.\nGreat for avatars looking to brighten their wardrobe with practical yet stylish pieces.\nComplements neutral tops and accessories for a balanced look.</string>

    <string name="pant_pink_baggy_cargo_pants">Embrace a trendy and comfortable style with these pink baggy cargo pants.\nPerfect for avatars seeking a blend of fashion-forward design and ease of movement.\nPairs well with fitted tops to balance the voluminous silhouette.</string>

    <string name="pant_pink_white_y2k_cargo_pants">Capture the Y2K aesthetic with these pink-white cargo pants, featuring a nostalgic design.\nIdeal for avatars wanting to relive early 2000s fashion trends with a modern twist.\nPair with fitted tops and chunky sneakers to complete the retro-inspired ensemble.</string>

    <string name="pant_ripped_black_jeans">Add an edgy touch to your avatars wardrobe with these ripped black pants, featuring distressed details.\nPerfect for avatars aiming for a rebellious and fashion-forward look.\nCombine with graphic tees or leather jackets to enhance the bold appearance.</string>

    <string name="pant_super_light_baggy_wash_jeans">Embrace a relaxed and airy vibe with these super light baggy jeans, offering comfort and style.\nIdeal for avatars seeking a casual and effortless look for everyday wear.\nPair with simple t-shirts or tank tops to maintain a laid-back aesthetic.</string>

    <string name="pant_urban_medium_cargo_jeans">Blend city chic with practicality in these urban cargo pants, featuring multiple pockets and a sleek design.\nGreat for avatars who appreciate functional fashion suitable for urban adventures.\nMatches well with hoodies, sneakers, or casual jackets for a street-smart ensemble.</string>

    <string name="pant_white_sweatpants">Relax in style with these white sweatpants, offering a clean and comfortable option for loungewear.\nPerfect for avatars prioritizing comfort without compromising on a fresh appearance.\nCombine with hoodies or casual tees for a cozy and laid-back outfit.</string>

    <string name="pant_white_y2k_cargo_pants">Introduce versatility to your avatars wardrobe with these white cargo pants, suitable for various styles.\nIdeal for avatars seeking a neutral base that can be dressed up or down for different occasions.\nPairs well with colorful tops or monochrome pieces for a cohesive look.</string>

    <string name="pant_y2k_wide_cargo_black_pant">Make a statement with these black wide cargo pants, combining boldness with functionality.\nSuitable for avatars aiming for a strong and confident appearance with ample pocket space.\nComplements fitted tops and boots to balance the wide-leg silhouette.</string>

    <string name="tee_baggy_off_band_shirt">Embrace a relaxed, vintage-inspired look with this baggy off-band shirt, featuring a loose fit and distressed band graphics.\nIdeal for avatars seeking a casual, laid-back style with a touch of rock and roll attitude.\nPair with skinny jeans or shorts to balance the oversized silhouette.</string>

    <string name="tee_black_crop_top">This versatile black crop top offers a sleek and modern aesthetic, perfect for various casual and semi-formal occasions.\nIts fitted design accentuates the figure, making it a staple piece for any wardrobe.\nCombine with high-waisted pants or skirts for a balanced and chic ensemble.</string>

    <string name="tee_black_silver_cross_top">Make a bold statement with this black top adorned with a striking silver cross design, exuding a gothic and edgy vibe.\nIdeal for avatars looking to showcase a unique and rebellious style.\nPair with dark accessories and bottoms to complete the look.</string>

    <string name="tee_black_tank_top">A classic black tank top that serves as a versatile foundation for various outfits, offering comfort and style.\nPerfect for layering or wearing solo during warmer days.\nMatch with jeans, shorts, or skirts for a simple yet fashionable appearance.</string>

    <string name="tee_blue_tube_top">Add a pop of color to your wardrobe with this vibrant blue tube top, featuring a strapless design for a chic and summery feel.\nGreat for avatars seeking a fun and flirty outfit option.\nPair with high-waisted shorts or skirts to create a balanced silhouette.</string>

    <string name="tee_emo">Channel the alternative scene with this EMO tee, showcasing bold graphics and a dark color palette.\nIdeal for avatars expressing their unique style and musical influences.\nCombine with skinny jeans and studded accessories for an authentic emo look.</string>

    <string name="tee_heart_baby">This adorable heart baby tee features a cute heart graphic, adding a touch of sweetness to any outfit.\nPerfect for avatars aiming for a playful and youthful appearance.\nPair with denim overalls or skirts for a charming ensemble.</string>

    <string name="tee_leopard_tank_top">Unleash your wild side with this leopard print tank top, offering a bold and trendy look.\nIdeal for avatars seeking to make a fashion statement with animal prints.\nCombine with neutral bottoms to let the top stand out.</string>

    <string name="tee_pink_crop_top">Brighten your wardrobe with this vibrant pink crop top, perfect for adding a pop of color to your ensemble.\nIts fitted design and short length make it ideal for warm weather and casual outings.\nPair with high-waisted jeans or skirts for a balanced and trendy look.</string>

    <string name="tee_pink_ruffle_sleeves">Add a touch of femininity to your outfit with this pink tee featuring delicate ruffle sleeves.\nIdeal for avatars seeking a soft and charming appearance.\nCombine with light-colored bottoms and subtle accessories for a cohesive look.</string>

    <string name="tee_purple">Stand out with this rich purple tee, offering a vibrant hue to elevate your casual wardrobe.\nIts classic design ensures versatility and comfort for everyday wear.\nPair with neutral or complementary colored bottoms for a harmonious ensemble.</string>

    <string name="tee_secret_service">Showcase a mysterious and authoritative vibe with this Secret Service tee, featuring bold lettering and a sleek design.\nPerfect for avatars aiming for a strong and confident appearance.\nCombine with dark sunglasses and tailored bottoms to complete the look.</string>

    <string name="tee_star">Shine bright with this black tee adorned with star graphics, adding a celestial touch to your outfit.\nIdeal for avatars seeking a trendy and eye-catching design.\nPair with denim or metallic accessories to enhance the stellar theme.</string>

    <string name="tee_tube_top_black">This classic black tube top offers a sleek and minimalist look, perfect for various occasions.\nIts strapless design provides a chic and modern aesthetic.\nCombine with high-waisted bottoms and statement jewelry for a polished ensemble.</string>

    <string name="tee_white">A timeless wardrobe staple, this white tee offers endless versatility and comfort.\nIdeal for layering or wearing on its own for a clean and classic look.\nPair with virtually any bottom to create a simple yet stylish ensemble.</string>

    <string name="tee_white_bow_top">Elevate your style with this chic white bow top, featuring a voluminous bow at the front that extends over one shoulder, creating an asymmetric neckline.\nDesigned with a fitted silhouette, it includes silicone trim inside the upper edge and boning at the front and back for added shape and support.\nA concealed zipper at the back with a hook-and-eye fastener ensures a seamless finish.\nPerfect for avatars seeking a sophisticated and elegant look.\nPair with tailored trousers or a sleek skirt to complete the ensemble.</string>

    <string name="tee_white_crop_top">This classic white crop top offers a sleek and minimalist look, perfect for various occasions.\nIts fitted design and short length make it ideal for warm weather and casual outings.\nCombine with high-waisted jeans or skirts for a balanced and trendy appearance.</string>

    <string name="tee_y2k_california_crop_top">Capture the essence of early 2000s West Coast fashion with this Y2K California crop top, featuring vintage-inspired graphics and a fitted silhouette.\nPerfect for avatars seeking a casual and trendy look that pays homage to the Y2K era.\nCombine with denim shorts or cargo pants for a laid-back, beach-ready outfit.</string>

    <string name="tee_y2k_star_baby_tee">Embrace the nostalgic Y2K aesthetic with this star baby tee, featuring a fitted design and playful star graphics reminiscent of early 2000s fashion trends.\nIdeal for avatars looking to capture a fun and youthful vibe.\nPair with low-rise jeans or mini skirts to complete the throwback ensemble.</string>

    <string name="shirt_adidas_knitted_top">Elevate your avatars athletic style with the Adidas Knitted Top, featuring a comfortable and sleek design.\nPerfect for avatars seeking a blend of sportswear and casual fashion.\nPair with track pants or jeans to achieve a versatile and trendy look.</string>

    <string name="shirt_ardor_open_zip_hoodie">Enhance your avatar\'s streetwear ensemble with the Ardor Open Zip Hoodie in black, offering a modern and edgy appearance.\nIdeal for avatars aiming for a casual yet stylish outfit.\nCombine with joggers or ripped jeans to complete the urban look.</string>

    <string name="shirt_ardor_open_zip_hoodie_grey">Introduce a neutral tone to your avatar\'s wardrobe with the Ardor Open Zip Hoodie in grey, providing a balanced and versatile option.\nSuitable for avatars desiring a laid-back and adaptable style.\nMatches well with various bottoms, from casual shorts to classic denim.</string>

    <string name="shirt_bandana_top_black">Add a bohemian flair to your avatar\'s attire with the Bandana Top, featuring a unique pattern and design.\nGreat for avatars looking to express a free-spirited and artistic vibe.\nPair with high-waisted shorts or skirts to enhance the eclectic aesthetic.</string>

    <string name="shirt_black_cropped_zip_hoodie">Showcase a chic and modern look with the Black Cropped Zip Hoodie, offering a trendy twist on a classic piece.\nPerfect for avatars aiming for a fashionable and comfortable outfit.\nCombine with high-rise jeans or leggings to complete the ensemble.</string>

    <string name="shirt_black_trendy_school_top">Embrace a youthful and stylish appearance with the Black Trendy School Hoodie, ideal for a casual day out.\nSuitable for avatars seeking a blend of comfort and fashion.\nPair with sneakers and a backpack to complete the school-inspired look.</string>

    <string name="shirt_black_white_bandage_top">Make a bold statement with the Black and White Bandage Top, featuring a striking contrast design.\nIdeal for avatars looking to stand out with a unique and edgy style.\nCombine with minimalist accessories to let the top be the focal point of the outfit.</string>

    <string name="shirt_blue_bandage_crop_top">Infuse a pop of color into your avatar\'s wardrobe with the Blue Bandage Crop Top, offering a vibrant and trendy look.\nGreat for avatars aiming to showcase confidence and style.\nPair with neutral bottoms to balance the boldness of the top.</string>

    <string name="shirt_cute_summer_crop_top">Embrace the warmth with the Cute Summer Top, designed to keep your avatar cool and stylish during sunny days.\nPerfect for avatars seeking a light and breezy outfit.\nCombine with shorts or a flowy skirt to complete the summer-ready ensemble.</string>

    <string name="shirt_denim_tears_hoodie">Add a touch of artistry to your avatar\'s look with the Denim Tears Hoodie, featuring a unique design that stands out.\nIdeal for avatars wanting to express individuality and creativity.\nPair with simple bottoms to let the hoodie be the centerpiece of the outfit.</string>

    <string name="shirt_leopard_folded_top">Introduce a wild side to your avatar\'s wardrobe with the Leopard Folded Top, showcasing a fierce animal print.\nGreat for avatars looking to make a bold fashion statement.\nCombine with black jeans or skirts to complement the striking pattern.</string>

    <string name="shirt_leopard_print_tied_top">Embrace a trendy and daring look with the Leopard Tied Top, featuring a stylish knot design.\nSuitable for avatars aiming to showcase confidence and flair.\nPair with high-waisted bottoms to balance the cropped fit of the top.</string>

    <string name="shirt_miami_off_shoulder">Capture a relaxed and elegant vibe with the Miami Off-Shoulder Top in white, perfect for a beach-inspired look.\nIdeal for avatars seeking a blend of comfort and sophistication.\nCombine with light-colored bottoms to maintain a fresh and airy ensemble.</string>

    <string name="shirt_miami_off_shoulder_black">Embrace a relaxed and elegant vibe with the Miami Off-Shoulder Top in black, perfect for a chic, beach-inspired look.\nIdeal for avatars seeking a blend of comfort and sophistication.\nPair with light-colored bottoms to maintain a fresh and airy ensemble.</string>

    <string name="shirt_oversized_black_crop_top">This oversized black crop top offers a modern essential with long sleeves and a crew neck, providing a relaxed yet chic look.\nCrafted from ultra-soft 100% cotton, it\'s ideal for layering over sports bras or wearing solo for an athleisure vibe.\nThe raw edge hem adds a touch of edginess to the classic black design.</string>

    <string name="shirt_oversized_white_crop_top">This oversized white crop top offers a fresh and clean aesthetic, suitable for various casual occasions.\nIts relaxed fit and soft fabric ensure all-day comfort.\nPair it with jeans or shorts for a laid-back look.</string>

    <string name="shirt_oxford_off_shoulder">Combining classic and contemporary styles, the Oxford Off-Shoulder top features a unique off-shoulder design with a traditional oxford shirt look.\nIt\'s perfect for those seeking a blend of sophistication and modern flair.\nIdeal for both office wear and casual outings.</string>

    <string name="shirt_striped_oversized_top">This top boasts a timeless striped pattern with an oversized fit, making it a comfortable yet stylish choice.\nThe versatile design allows it to be dressed up or down, suitable for various occasions.\nIts breathable fabric ensures comfort throughout the day.</string>

    <string name="shirt_white_oversized_sweater">A cozy addition to any wardrobe, this white oversized sweater provides warmth and style.\nIts loose fit makes it perfect for layering during cooler seasons.\nThe neutral color offers endless pairing possibilities with different bottoms and accessories.</string>

    <string name="shirt_y2k_red_paid_christmas_outfit">Embrace the festive spirit with this Y2K-inspired red plaid Christmas outfit.\nThe ensemble includes a stylish top that captures the holiday vibe, making it perfect for seasonal gatherings and celebrations.\nIts trendy design ensures you\'ll stand out during the festivities.</string>

    <string name="face_angry">Expresses a strong feeling of displeasure or hostility.\nIdeal for avatars needing to convey frustration or anger.\nPair with intense animations or gestures to enhance the effect.</string>

    <string name="face_cute_smile">Displays a charming and endearing smile.\nPerfect for avatars aiming to appear friendly and approachable.\nCombine with cheerful animations to amplify the warmth.</string>

    <string name="face_eye_blink">Shows a quick closing and opening of the eyelids.\nUseful for adding realism and subtlety to avatar expressions.\nIncorporate into idle animations for a natural appearance.</string>

    <string name="face_look_at_my_nose">Directs the avatar\'s gaze towards its own nose.\nIdeal for playful or curious expressions.\nUse in scenarios where the avatar is examining something closely.</string>

    <string name="face_scared">Conveys fear or apprehension.\nSuitable for avatars in frightening or surprising situations.\nEnhance with trembling animations for added effect.</string>

    <string name="face_sigmund">Features a thoughtful and analytical expression.\nGreat for avatars portraying deep thinking or contemplation.\nPair with pondering gestures to emphasize introspection.</string>

    <string name="face_silly_fun">Exhibits a playful and goofy demeanor.\nPerfect for avatars engaging in lighthearted activities.\nCombine with exaggerated movements for comedic effect.</string>

    <string name="face_sly_guy_face">Displays a cunning and mischievous look.\nIdeal for avatars plotting or teasing.\nUse with subtle animations to convey sneakiness.</string>

    <string name="face_teeth_smile">Shows a broad smile revealing teeth.\nGreat for avatars expressing happiness and joy.\nPair with upbeat animations to enhance the cheerful vibe.</string>

    <string name="face_tongy_smile">Displays a playful smile with the tongue sticking out.\nSuitable for avatars in a teasing or joking mood.\nCombine with winking animations for added playfulness.</string>


    <string name="hair_barided">A hairstyle featuring interlaced strands, creating intricate patterns close to the scalp.\nIdeal for avatars seeking a traditional or cultural appearance.\nPair with accessories like beads or ribbons to enhance the look.</string>

    <string name="hair_black_layered">Features multiple layers of sleek, black hair, adding volume and movement.\nPerfect for avatars desiring a classic and versatile hairstyle.\nComplements both casual and formal outfits seamlessly.</string>

    <string name="hair_fluffy_white">A voluminous hairstyle with soft, white tresses, exuding a whimsical charm.\nGreat for avatars aiming for a playful or ethereal look.\nPairs well with fantasy-themed attire or vibrant accessories.</string>

    <string name="hair_layered_wavy_valley_girl">Combines layered cuts with natural waves, offering a relaxed, beach-inspired vibe.\nIdeal for avatars seeking a laid-back yet stylish appearance.\nEnhances casual outfits and adds a touch of effortless chic.</string>

    <string name="hair_medium_middle_part">Medium-length hair parted down the center, providing a balanced and symmetrical look.\nSuitable for avatars desiring a straightforward and adaptable hairstyle.\nComplements a variety of face shapes and fashion styles.</string>

    <string name="hair_orange_beanie_with_black">Black hair styled under a vibrant orange beanie, adding a pop of color and casual flair.\nPerfect for avatars aiming for a trendy, street-style appearance.\nPairs well with urban outfits and casual wear.</string>

    <string name="hair_pony_tail">Hair gathered and secured at the back of the head, allowing for a clean and practical style.\nIdeal for avatars seeking a sporty or professional look.\nVersatile and complements both activewear and business attire.</string>

    <string name="hair_rainbow_coloured">Vibrant hair featuring a spectrum of colors, making a bold and expressive statement.\nGreat for avatars looking to showcase a creative and unique style.\nEnhances artistic outfits and stands out in any crowd.</string>

    <string name="hair_valentines">A romantic hairstyle, often incorporating soft curls or waves, perfect for special occasions.\nSuitable for avatars aiming for an elegant and affectionate appearance.\nComplements formal wear and adds a touch of romance to any ensemble.</string>

    <string name="hair_wavy_middle_part">Features gentle waves parted in the center, offering a relaxed yet polished look.\nIdeal for avatars desiring a natural and effortless hairstyle.\nPairs well with both casual and semi-formal outfits.</string>


    <string name="head_cheeks">Features full and prominent cheeks, adding a youthful and rounded appearance to the face.\nIdeal for avatars seeking a soft and approachable look.\nComplements hairstyles that frame the face, enhancing the fullness of the cheeks.</string>

    <string name="head_chiseled">Exhibits well-defined facial features with sharp angles, often associated with a strong jawline and high cheekbones.\nPerfect for avatars desiring a striking and sculpted appearance.\nPairs well with short hairstyles that highlight facial structure.</string>

    <string name="head_narrow">Characterized by a face that is longer than it is wide, with a slender overall appearance.\nSuitable for avatars aiming for an elegant and elongated facial profile.\nWorks well with hairstyles that add width, such as waves or curls, to balance proportions.</string>

    <string name="head_paragon">Represents an idealized facial structure with balanced proportions and symmetrical features.\nIdeal for avatars seeking a harmonious and universally appealing look.\nVersatile with various hairstyles, allowing for flexibility in personal styling.</string>

    <string name="head_strong_jaw">Features a prominent and angular jawline, conveying strength and determination.\nGreat for avatars desiring a bold and assertive facial appearance.\nComplements hairstyles that soften the jawline, such as layered cuts or styles with volume at the crown.</string>

    <string name="head_trim">Showcases a slim and well-maintained facial structure with subtle contours.\nIdeal for avatars seeking a neat and refined appearance.\nPairs well with sleek hairstyles that mirror the face\'s streamlined profile.</string>

</resources>